Next Preview
Hey, I'm looking at you!
The t-shirt is so cute! I've seen a sample of the actual t-shirt once before, a few months ago.
I've seen a sample of it once before, but this is the first time I've seen it made into a t-shirt, so I'm very happy.
This is the point here, the line here.
It's so cute... we had a lot of different choices, but I'm so glad we went with this color.
We had about 3 different colors and 3 different patterns for the blue, and we decided on this one.
This was the main idea, but it was completed with everyone's input.
How do you like it?
I'm going to choose the blue one.
I chose blue.
I chose the blue one.
I'm looking at it right now.
none
manou a manou
pedro
me
Is it?
I like it.
Yes, yes, OK
Yes, OK.
OK, the last one.
OK.
Cute.
Bitter?
No, no.
What?
Good night, sweetie.
Good night, sweetheart.
Good night.
Yes, sir.
Hands.
hand
A hairdresser's story
So cute!
Beauty
The fabric is firm and not see through.
I can easily cut it with just one piece.
The color scheme is just so cute!
It's so cute!
Even if you don't know me as a hairdresser
I think it's a character of a cute girl.
I think it's a cute girl character.
But of course, if you know anything about beauty
For those who know us...
We're wearing beauty clothes!
Like, "Hey, we're wearing beauty clothes!
I think people will wear it.
I hope you wear it a lot.
Please wear it a lot.
It's cute.
They're cute.
They're all cute.
Oh, it's good, it's good, it's good.
They were cute!
It was fun shooting
Thank you so much!
Now it's time to get together
I'll do my best.
Do you have eye contact now?
Yes, sir.
Thank you for your hard work.
One more time.
Shut up.
I like it.
Just a little more.
Please...
Please.
Finally
One more time
Wave to me
Finally
Please.
One more time.
Oh, yes, yes!
Yes!YES!!!
Time has stopped.
Please.
I felt a real sense of accomplishment. It was like we had completed something that we had thought of.
I am happy.
I am happy to know that what we have created together, with the participation of all the members, has become a work of art,
I feel that we are able to shoot the film,
I guess it's a nationwide project.
That's right.
Japan debut!
Today, Ikuta-san told me that he was selected as the Japanese representative for the collar.
I have to work even harder because I didn't make it to the Japan national team.
I will continue to do so.
We don't often do shoots where the clothes are shown off well.
That was also very fresh for me,
I wanted to learn more.
I wanted to learn more about the back view and so on.
What did you think?
I realized today that I still have a long way to go in terms of looking back,
So I thought I would practice it every day before going to bed.
Flexibility is important!
I will do my best.
I'm glad.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's so cute!
It looks like it will be active in summer!
It looks like it will play an active part in a nice summer!
By the way, this is
Project T-shirts.
Here's Angstrom!
Are you wearing it?
Yes, I am.
In the back...
Keep Yo Smile
The colors are so pretty.
I love it.
So pretty.
But so cute
Thanks for the help.
It's cute.
Look at Asako-san.
I'm off.
How is it?
What do you think?
What do you think? I'm already looking at this completed T-shirt.
I'm wearing the T-shirt that I drew.
I feel strange that I am wearing it and taking pictures of it.
Indeed.
It's really cute.
It's hard to do.
The fact that I have to show the T-shirt.
It's difficult, isn't it?
It was difficult. Very difficult.
I always want to put my hands here and there.
So it was difficult to show the T-shirt.
Yes, it was.
Yes.
Yes. - Yes.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Oh! That's great! And it's backwards!
Oh! Yum!
Did you bring it?
Thank you so much!
Okay, the three of us just finished the photo shoot.
I'm wearing it for the first time today, and it's the first time I've seen the tissue that you guys designed for me, and it's so cute!
The stylish texture and the tea horse log are so cute, I'm so excited!
I'm wearing the 25th anniversary T-shirt, and I want you to look at the back.
It has a cute and colorful tea horse logo on it.
I love it so much that I took this picture so that you can see the back print on the back.
I was really good at it, but I had to capture the face as well, so I had a bit of a hard time with that.
I struggled a little with that part, but I had the best twists from the beginning.
I was so happy to get the best twist.
How do you like it, Lulia?
It was the first time for me to wear the finished cat ear cuff with everyone.
It's a three-dimensional version of the logo.
And here's a cup of tea.
Here...
Isn't it cute?
Are you saying that this stick is a tea pole?
Yes, yes.
That's what I mean.
Chabashira in the preview.
I really like the way you made it look and it's really cute.
I hope everyone will get one!I hope everyone will get one!
Get it!
From there, slowly.
Ah, yes!
You're doing great.
My legs and here, my muscles might be strong.
That's a lie.
That's great!
Okay, just a little more.
Yes, yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, we're done.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Yes, we are done.
This time, we collaborated with Jinyu on the products,
We, Tsubaki, designed a T-shirt and a necklace.
The back is like this.
Each member's face is in the picture,
It looks like an ordinary shot.
It looks like an off-shot.
It's an off-shot kind of shot.
This necklace is also here,
Marin Fukuda, a member, wrote "Tsubaki" on it.
Isn't it amazing?
I want to go there.
I can't write like this, can I?
I can't.
I can't write like this.
I've been rewriting a lot,
I worked so hard on it,
I'm so happy that it's now a product.
It's true.
First of all, I hope that Marin's fans will get it.
And also those who like us,
And those who like Tsubaki.
Even if you don't like Tsubaki,
I thought it was cute.
It's fashionable.
You can wear it in everyday life.
It looks wearable.
You can definitely wear it in everyday life.
These coordinates are cute.
Stylish.
I like this one too. I like this one here.
It has flowers on it.
Flowers, too.
It looks like it goes with everything.
Shikari balne is cute, isn't it?
It goes with everything.
I'd love to see you wear it to a live concert or something,
I hope you will come to our concerts and see us.
Please get one.
So, there you have it, a look at the photo shoot with GU!
The GU and Hello! Project collaboration item that we are wearing now will be on sale!
Please get it!
We did our best, so please take a look!
Please buy it! Please buy it!